{
    "about": [
    {
        "question": "Who's your favorite artist?",
        "answer": "Hins Cheung."
    },
    {
        "question": "When you started programming?",
        "answer": "To be precise, since 2020."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why Computer Science?",
        "answer": "I found interest in software engineering during my major in Information Security and therefore decided to focus on this aspect."
    },
    {
        "question": "How long have you learned singing?",
        "answer": "Since the summer of 2021."
    },
    {
        "question": "What's your favorite framework?",
        "answer": "NextJS."
    },
    {
        "question": "What's your most hated programming language?",
        "answer": "PHP."
    },
    {
        "question": "Any advice for your past self?",
        "answer": "Don't go to HKUST."
    },
    {
        "question": "What you do in your leisure time?",
        "answer": "Singing, Hangout w/ friends, Watching YouTube/Twitch/Netflix..."
    },
    {
        "question": "What music are you into?",
        "answer": "Pop, Lofi, Acoustic, Alternative Rock."
    },
    {
        "question": "Dogs or Cats?",
        "answer": "Both."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why you make this section?",
        "answer": "Idk, it looks cool."
    },
    {
        "question": "What sports do you like?",
        "answer": "Bouldering and Badminton."
    },
    {
        "question": "What's your favorite food?",
        "answer": "Sushi, Tea egg, Fried squid..."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who do you think will see this?",
        "answer": "You."
    },
    {
        "question": "How relevant/updated is this website?",
        "answer": "You can check the last update in the footer."
    },
    {
        "question": "Any reason to reach out?",
        "answer": "I need friends :("
    }
    ]
}